rentmystay.com 2015-04-30

# Privacy Policy - RentMyStay.com

Please read this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") carefully before using RentMyStay.com (the "Site"). By accessing, browsing and using the Website, you acknowledge that you have read and understand this Policy. This Policy applies to your use of this Website only; should you follow a link on this Website to another Website, you are no longer covered by this Policy.

BrightPath Technology and services pvt Ltd, (hereinafter "we," "us," "RentMyStay") owns and operates the Site. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, with or without notice.

##  User-provided information

We collect personal information when you register or add a property listing or submit enquiry, including but not limited to your email address, phone number, and mailing address (the "Personal Information"). If you are listing a property, we will also collect property-specific information including but not limited to amenities, rates, policies, and location (the "Property Information"). We may use your Personal Information to contact you from time to time with customer updates and information, or to send you information about new services or opportunities. You will be able to "opt out" of receiving marketing information by changing your notification settings on the dashboard. However, as a condition of maintaining your account, we will have the right to contact you at any time regarding your account. Should you not wish to receive further contact from us, you have the option of deactivating your account.

We will not share your information with third parties, except: (i) in the case of special promotions by RentMyStay or a third-party (unless you have elected to "opt out" of receiving marketing information;) (ii) where a third party performs services on behalf of RentMyStay and has agreed to keep such information confidential (such as processing your credit card payment or conducting an online survey); and (iii) the aggregate use of the information of multiple RentMyStay users where individual Personal Information is not disclosed. We may share Website usage information about users with a third-party tracking company for the purposes of reporting statistics. For this purpose, some of the pages you visit on the Website use tracking mechanisms such as pixel tags (also called clear gifs). We may also use your information to market our services and to gain feedback on potential new services. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information and/or Property Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

##  User Communications

Users of the Website may send email/Broadcast/Shout-out enquiries to Hosts and service providers and/or provide email responses via clickable links on the Website. If you choose to utilize such link or links, your Personal Information and/or Property Information may become known to the third party with whom you are communicating. Do not share such information that you are not prepared to allow such parties to have, including, but not limited to credit card and bank account information. We may also retain these email enquiries and/or responses. While the content of these email enquiries and/or responses is not shared with any other party, we may from time to time use third party email servers to send and track receipt of such enquiry/response emails, and analyze the pattern of enquiry/response usage via these third-party tracking systems.

## Protection of your information

RentMyStay encrypts and stores all personal information, including credit card information, on a secured server. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption for information you may provide on our booking process or online signup process. Please be aware, however, that no transmission of information via the Internet can be entirely secure. You should, therefore, always use caution when submitting personal information online. We take commercially reasonable steps to provide security for your information once we receive it. We do not share, sell, rent, or trade personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information, Property Information, or other information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website. We use a credit card processing company to bill property Hosts for services and to collect booking charges. To the best of our knowledge, these companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

##  Change of personal information

Should you want to change or access your Personal Information, you may do so on the Website under your Profile. To protect your privacy and security, we will verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your Personal Information and/or Property Information.

##  Cookies

RentMyStay may use cookies to store some of your personal preferences for future visits. A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a web server to store in a web browser so that it can later be read back from that browser. Cookies allow us to recognize you more quickly; therefore, your time spent on the Website can be more personalized and productive. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any Personal Information you submit while on our Website.

We may use third-party Website usage tracking companies to analyze use of the Website or to conduct surveys. In the course of serving the Website, these third parties may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to the Website and other websites in order to help us understand how to serve you better. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

##  Reviews and customer feedback

RentMyStay sometimes receives testimonials and comments from Website users wishing to share their booking and/or travel experiences. We may publish such content from time to time. By submitting such testimonials and comments, you grant us permission to publish such content at our sole discretion. Please be aware that any Personal Information, Property Information, or other information you submit can be read, collected or used by other users of this Website and you could be sent unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the Personal Information, Property Information or other information which you choose to submit for testimonials.

##  Surveys or contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our Website. If you participate, we will request certain Personal Information and or other information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose such information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code). We use this information to award prizes and to continually improve the user experience at RentMyStay. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company is prohibited from using our users' Personal Information for any other purpose.

##  Other limitations

While RentMyStay takes reasonable steps to safeguard and to prevent unauthorized access to your information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied, or otherwise, that we will prevent unauthorized access to your private information.

IN NO EVENT SHALL RentMyStay BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES (WHETHER CONSEQUENTIAL, DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL OR OTHERWISE) ARISING OUT OF, OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH, A THIRD PARTY'S UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, THE PROPERTY INFORMATION, OR ANY OTHER USER PROVIDED INFORMATION REGARDLESS OF WHETHER SUCH DAMAGES ARE BASED ON CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, TORT OR OTHER THEORIES OF LIABILITY, AND ALSO REGARDLESS OF WHETHER RentMyStay WAS GIVEN ACTUAL OR CONSTRUCTIVE NOTICE THAT DAMAGES WERE POSSIBLE.

ALL LEGAL MATTERS SHALL BE SETTLED AT COURTS IN BANGALORE ONLY.
